ILGWU Communications Department Photographs 5780/176 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- New Jersey (Box 11, Folder 2a)
  Includes ILGers demonstrating in front of Congressman Bob Franks' office, 1993; Local 133 at the NJ Gasoline Retailers' Association Convention, Ellenville, NY, 1994; Cutters from Evan Picone's, 1990; Italian-American Labor Council Pres. and ILG NJ Dir. Salvatore Giardina and AFL-CIO Sec'y-Treas. Tom Donohue, 1995; Frank Camerone, president of the Bergen-Hudson District, 1994; Giardina and NJ Governor Jim Florio, 1993; Health Fair, 1993; Sen. Frank Lautenberg with ILGers at rally, Newark, 1992; ILGers rally for jobs, 1992; Education Director Ira Stern, 1992; ILGers with Perth Amboy Mayor Joseph Vas, 1992; Workers at Alexandra Fashions, North Bergen, 1990; Gov. Florio, VP Giardina and Virgil Bavaro, manager of Essex District Council, 1991; District Manager Eli Charne, 1992; ILGers of the Passaic District, 1991; Day care at health conference, 1990; Charne and Business Agent Magdalena Velez, 1992; Newark Retirees Club at CPR training course, 1991; Workers at Petrie Stores, Secaucus, 1991; Labor Commissioner Ray Bramucci and Giardina, 1991; ILGers, Passaic, 1990; Strikers at Teximpor, 1990; ILGers at National Health Care rally, Liberty State Park, 1990; Judge Daniel O'Hern and Bramucci, 1990; Workers at Roxanne, 1990; ILG VP Evelyn Dubrow with ILGers of new Southern New Jersey Chapter of Coalition of Labor Union Workers (CLUW), 1993; ILGers at Mariners Astubeco, 1990; ILG Bergen-Hudson District Manager Eli Charne, 1990; George Benson, assistant manager of the union's Essex District Council and Mgr. Virgil Bavaro with ILGers collecting gifts for Persian Gulf soldiers, 1990; Central District Pres. Inez Moore and VP Mamie Zaremba, 1989; Roy Kirkley, director of the Labor Education Center and Clara Dasher of the Newark Teachers Union, 1989; George Dumenigo, union social worker, 1987
- New York District (Box 11, Folder 3)
  Includes Pres. Jay Mazur, VP Giardina and others meeting with Italian trade unionists, 1993; Mademoiselle shop unionists and representatives, 1992; Workers at Point Blank, Amityville, 1990; Workers from Joe-Jim Fashions, 1991; Workers from D'Ambrosio Textile Co, 1991; Workers from Knitting Mills, Bellmore, 1991; Nassau-Suffolk District Mgr. Mike Grimaldi and NY State Dist. Organizing Dir. David Munck with workers of Thermo-Vu Sunlite Industries, Brentwood, 1992; NY Deputy Mayor of Finance Sally-Hernandez-Pinero with Pres. Jay Mazur and Eli Elias, pres. of the NY Skirt and Sporstwear Assoc., 1990; ILGers at good health workshops, 1990; ILGers lobbying for improved Workers' Compensation law, 1990; Seneca Knitting Mills, 1990; Workers from Seneca Knitting Mills, 1990; "First Convention for Women's Rights" sign, 1990; "B. Altman & Co. is closed" signs, 1990; ILGWU health workshop, Amityville, 1990
- New York District (Box 11, Folder 4)
  Includes - ILGers at Thermo-Vu negotiations, 1990; Thermo-Vu workers, 1990; ILGers from local 10, 1988; ILGWU tennis tournament to raise money for cancer research, Westchester, 1988; Upstate NY Dist. members at meeting, Glen Falls, 1988; ILG Upstate Dist. Mgr. Judith Conley at dinner, 1986; VP Barbara Laufman, Asst. General Counsel Lester Kushner and Upstate Mgr. Judy Conley, 1988; Westchester-Putnam AFL-CIO Pres. Peter Puglia with ILGers, 1987; Nassau-Suffolk Dist. Council Mgr. Mary Ruggiero, 1987; Judith Conley, 1986; ILGers completing their Health and Exercise classes, Yonkers, 1986; Lower Hudson Dist. Council Mgr. Mike Trinchi and Representative Hamilton, 1987; Mike Trinchi and others lobbying for Congressman Joseph DioGuardi, 1986; ILGWU Lower Hudson Valley Dist. Council in the "March of Dimes Walkathon", 1986; Assemblyman Richard Brodsky receiving endorsement from Trinchi and Assemblyman Ron Tocci, 1989; VP Sal Giardina, former Oswego mayor John Fitzgibbons honoring ILG veteran, 1986
- Northeast W., Pa. and Ohio (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Includes Senator Arlen Specter, VP Joe Fisher, dir. of the Eastern Pa. Region, Irwin Solomon, ILG General Sec'y-Treas., Pres. Jay Mazur and VP Evelyn Dubrow, 1986; Members plan a phone tree in the event of a strike, 1988; ILGers at parade marking the anniversary of Johnstown flood of 1889; Lois Hartel, Manager of the Hazelton and Wyoming Valley Dist., 1989; Leafletting at Katrina Mfg., Williamsport; Shamokin-Sunbury workers leafleting, 1983; 50-year working veteran at Shamokin Dress, 1989; Little Miss USA, 1988; Workers at Rossmor Industries reviewing new agreement, 1987; Vickie Smeltzer, chairperson at Toby Sportswear honored by the United Way,1988; ILGers at NQII LTD., 1988; ILGers in parade, Mount Carmel, 1988; Ohio State Dir. Albert Gargiulo swearing in new directors, 1988; Tom Mathews, mgr. of the Shamokin-Sunbury-Pottsville Dis., 1987; The Wilkes-Barre(PA) ILGWU chorus, 1987; Workers at J.K. Operating Corp., Kulpmont, 1987; Workers from Bestform Foundations, Johnstown, 1987; Leon Stein signs his book, "Triangle Fire", at Bucknell University, 1986; VP Ron Alman and VP Edgar Romney with Volunteer Organizing Committee (VOC) members, Harrisburg, PA, 1987
- Northeast W., Pa. and Ohio (Box 12, Folder 2)
  Includes Health care cartoon by Huck Konkapaka, 1986; ILG strikers at Pittston, 1986; Pres. Jay Mazur and Northeast Dept. Asst. Dir. Martin Berger with retiree, 1986; Local 93 Mgr. Joe Rotell with newly organized Zayre workers, 1987; ILGers volunteer to support Wofford, 1991; Wilkes-Barre ILGWU chorus, 1991; Participants in the Northeast Dept. Rank and File Leadership Conference, 1994; ILGers rally at Leslie Fay, NYC, 1993; ILGers celebrate victory, Tuscarora, PA, 1993; Penn. health fair, 1993; Bill Reck, education dir. of Pa. AFL-CIO and COPE Dir. Theresa Ruhl, 1994; Ohio Senator Robert Burch, speaks with ILGers, OH, 1994; AMES negotiating committee, 1994; Sam Bianco, pres. Wyoming Valley Central Labor Council and others supporting the United Way, 1994; ILGers at the holidays, Scranton, PA, 1994
- Northeast W., Pa. and Ohio (Box 12, Folder 3)
  Includes Lois Hartel and others burn the WARN notice of plant closing, 1993; "Valerie Belles", of Fashions Local 234-243, Wind Gap, PA, 1993; Calvin Klein with ILGers at Kaijay Pants. Co., Nesquehoning, PA, 1993; Local 196 members in parade, 1993; The Quality Inn negotiators, 1993; Congressman John Murtha (D-Pa.) with ILGers, 1993; George Pishko, former organizing dir. of the Northeast Dept. with Rosie Cappo, 1992; ILGers at Pa. Union Label Conference, Willke's Barre, 1992; ILGers in parade, Reading, PA, 1992; ILGers picket St. Luke's Hospital, PA, 1992; Sam Cavalieri, mgr. of Allentown Local 3, PA, 1992; Cleveland, Ohio ILGers in Union Counselor Classes, 1993; Easton ILGers, PA, 1993; Workers at Mary Fashions Mfg., Lehigh Valley, PA, 1991; PA ILGers support Lynn Yeakel for U.S. Senate, 1992; Pa. ILGers in "Negotiations Workshop" at Indiana U of PA, 1992; ILGers raise money in "Walk America", Johnstown, PA, 1990; ILGers at health fair, 1991; Wofford with PA ILGers, 1991; Steve Ulichney, Camsco Computer Marking, Wilkes-Barre, PA, 1990; ILGers participate in "March of Dimes", Easton, PA, 1989
- Northeast W., Pa. and Ohio (Box 12, Folder 4)
  Includes Ohio Dir. Al Gargiulo with ILGers, 1990; Governor Robert Casey signing the Medicare Overcharge Measure (MOM) bill. Pa.'s Somerset Mfg. celebrates 10th anniversary, 1990; Pictures of flood and damaged caused, 1990; ILG graduates of Cardio-Pulmonary Resuscitation (CPR) class, Lancaster, PA, 1990; March of Dimes Walk-a-thon, PA, 1991; Senator Harris Wofford with PA ILGers, 1991; ILGers at first aid classes, Groveport, OH, 1992; Fire drill at Cleveland Knitting Mills, marking the 1911 Triangle fire, 1992; Tom Mathews, asst. dir. of the ILGWU Northeast Dept., 1992; Workers at Jo-Ann Apparel in parade, Ebensburg, PA, 1992; ILGWU activists pose outside State Capitol in Harrisburg, PA, 1991; Sen. Wofford with ILGers, 1991; Meeting to win support fro the Workplace Fairness Act, 1991; Workers Memorial Day, 1991; VP Joseph Fisher opens talks with Knitted Outerwear Mfg. Assoc., PA, 1991; ILGWU at the Workers' Memorial Day Project, 1991; Ohio Local 298 members in Cleveland, 1991; Betty Miller, pres. Easton Dist. Council Local 234, 1991; Manager Jerry Gingrich of the Northern Dist. Council honoring member, 1991; ILGers lobbying in the Capitol rotunda, Harrisburg, PA, 1991; Northeast Dir. Sol Hoffman and Garguilo, 1991; Workers block entrance to Bestform Foundations, PA, 1993; Senator Wofford with ILGers at Linden Dress, 1994
- Shop Scenes Sewing (Box 12, Folder 5)
  Includes Arial views women at sewing machines; group shot women at sewing machines; women hand sewing coats; women hand sewing; woman threading a needle; close-ups of women at sewing machines; women at work; men sewing; Spools of thread/machines Long Island Yarn Company
- Finished Garments Transporting (Box 12, Folder 6)
  Includes Women wrapping clothing; Racks of wrapped clothing; men transporting clothing
- Organizations & Field Services (Box 12, Folder 7)
  Includes Strikers at Domsey Trading, Brooklyn, NY, 1990; V.P. Steve Nutter, General Organizer Joseph Danahy and others iron out T.J. Maxx pact, 1991; Clover Yarns members wearing T-Shirts "It's Our Future Everyone Counts.", 1991; Exec. VP Edgar Romney outside Domney Trading rally, 1991
- Organizations & Field Services (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Includes Strikers at Plastonics, Hartford, CT., Strikers at Domney Trading, 1991; Strikers at Mademoiselle, Brooklyn, NY, 1991; Strikers at Teammate Inc., 1989; Striking Performance workers, Bentonville, AK, 1993; City Councilman Sal Albanese, City Hall, NYC, 1989; ILG and CWA picketers at AT&T North Dade plant, 1986; Local 888 food workers on strike, 1994; Local 89-22-1 ILGers protest at D.J. Sportswear, 1994; STC workers leafleting consumers at JC Penney's, Queens, NY, 1993; Workers gain contract at Mademoiselle, 1992; Exec. VP Edgar Romney with Mademoiselle workers, 1992; Picketing outside Lasting Impressions, 1991; Pres. Jay Mazur with Organization and Field Services Director Joseph Danahy and Ann Hoffman, 1987; Graduates of the Organizers' Training Institute, NYC, 1988; Pres. Jay Mazur and Ken Dermota, 1987; Exec. VP Edgar Romney, 1987; Speakers from Cornell University and 21 organizing directors and executive directors from the ILGWU, North Brunswick, NJ, (circa 1990's); The Bay Bias organizing committee, San Francisco, CA, 1988; Joseph Danahy and UFW pres. Cesar Chavez, NYC, 1987; Strikers at La Mode, 1989; Strikers at Escada, NJ, 1989; Planning strategy for organizing drive at Domney, (circa 1990's); Strikers at Escada, NJ, 1989
- Organization & Field Services (Box 13, Folder 2)
  Includes - Participants in the Organizers' Training Program, 1986; Cartoon for "Health and Safety Enforcement" by Huck Konopacki, 1986; Chosun Daily News strikers, NYC, 1990; Professional and Clerical Employees (PACE) organizing director Brent Garren and formers workers from Korean News with back pay checks, 1993; AIM director Martin Berger, NJ Region BA Rosetta Lyons with Matawan workers, (circa 1990's); Counting ballots for PACE, NJ, (circa 1990's); PACE dir. Ann Hoffman with members of Matawan-Aberdeen; Strikers of Chosun Daily News, NYC, 1990; Exec. VP Edgar Romney and Sae Gae rally, NYC, 1991; Workers of Connecti COSH, 1992; Label for the ILGWU'S PACE, 1988; PACE director Ann Hoffman, VP Barbara Laufman and Safety dir. Becky Plattus, 1988; PACE rally, Columbia U, NYC, 1988
- PACE (Box 13, Folder 3)
  Includes Chosun Daily News strikers, 1990; Korea News workers get back pay checks, 1992; Matawan teachers vote to join PACE; Ann Hoffman with Matawan teachers; Chosun workers show NLRB papers, 1991; Sae Gae strikers, 1991; Ann Hoffman at press conference, 1988; Columbia university clerical workers strike, 1988
- Promotional Photos (Box 13, Folder 4)
  Includes Sheila Frazier, pres. Of Local 372, Sunnyvale, TX, 1994; Making of an ILG union label television ad, 1986
- Political Activity & Department (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Includes Reverend Jesse Jackson and others denounce California's Proposition 187, 1994; U.S. representative Nydia Velazquez with ILGers, 1994; NYC Congressman Charles Rangel and Political Director Ed Vargas with ILGers, 1995; Rep. Robert Menendez and BA Magdalena Velez during campaign, Hoboken, NJ, 1995; VP Sal Giardina, NJ Region Dir. with Industrial Union Council Pres. Bill Kane, 1994; Children in Poverty, 1992; Wisc. Congressman Tom Bennett, (circa 1990's); Cartoon for November vote by Huck Konkapaka, 1994; Sandy Sands, 1994; Sen. Edward Kennedy, 1992 ILGWU convention, 1994; Phil Bredesen, candidate for Tenn. Governor with ILGers, 1994; US Congresswoman Corrine Brown, 1994; Dan Siegelman, 1994; Larry Fortenberry, pres. of UAW Local 1155, Birmingham, GA, 1994; Tim Holden for Congress, 1994; Congressman John Lewis, 1992 ILGWU Convention, 1994 Western States Region Dir. Steve Nutter presents Candidate Kathleen Brown with check for her campaign, 1994; Bumberstick for "Jim Folson for Governor", 1994; Mike Doyle for Congress, 18th district, 1994; Senator Jim Sasser with ILGers, 1994; Barney Frank, 1994; Mario Cuomo, 1994; Senator Daniel Patrick Moynihan, 1994; Attorney General Candidate Karen Burstein1994; H. Carl McCall, Candidate for State Comptroller, 1994; Donald Payne, Candidate for US Representative, 1994; Congressman Robert Menendez at Genesis Knitting, Perth Amboy, NJ, 1994; NJ Congressman Herb Klein tours the Bloomfield Technical Machine Shop, 1994; Democratic candidate for PA Governor Mark Single with ILGers, 1994; Democratic Senator Charles Robb, 1994; Thelma Tibbs, President of AIM Chapter, #4 with Congressman Alan Wheat, 1994; C.J. Prentiss for State Representative, Bill Leavens for Congress, 1994; Bob Carr, US Senator, 1994; Wisconsin Senator Herb Kohl, 1994; Utah Representative Karen Shepard, 1994; Missouri Congressman William J. Clay, 1994; Tom Barlow for Congress from KT, 1994; Texas Congressman Gene Green, 1994
- Political Activity and Department (Box 13, Folder 6)
  Includes - Harlem Congressman Charles Rangel, 1994; NY Governor Mario Cuomo at Mademoiselle Knitwear, 1994; Rep. Major Owens with Domney strikers, 1994; Kathleen Brown for CA Governor, 1994; Governor candidate Mark Single with VP's Sol Hoffman and Joe Fisher, 1994; Senator Frank Lautenberg, 1994; US Senate Candidate Harris Wofford, 1994; Senator Jim Sasser, 1994; Congresswoman Carolyn Mahoney of NY, 1994; Pres. Jay Mazar with Rangel, 1994; NJ Governor Jim Florio, 1993; NY Mayor David Dinkins, 1993; Vice President Al Gore with ILG VP Lillian Grobmyer, 1993; Senator Russ Feingold of WS, 1993; California Senator Dianne Feinstein, 1992; Illinois Senator Carol Moseley Braun, 1992; ILGers in the Bronx, NY, 1992; ILGers in Chinatown, NY, 1992; Congressman Maurice Hinchey with ILGers, 1992; US Senate candidate Dianne Feinstein, 1992; US Senate candidate Chris Dodd, 1992; US Senate candidate Wyche Fowler, 1992; US Senate candidate Geri Rothman-Serot, 1992; US senate candidate Carol Moseley Brown, 1992; Pres. Jay Mazur with Nydia Velazquez, 1992; US Senate candidate Bob Abrams with NYC Mayor Dinkins, 1992; (newspaper clipping) Bill and Hillary Clinton, NYC, 1992; Political activist Sandra Buckner, 1990; Political activist Geraldine Wiley, 1990; Political activist Eleanor Kuhns, 1990; NJ Governor Jim Florio, 1990; NYC mayor David Dinkins, 1990; Several photos of Mayor Dinkins; Arkansas Governor Bill Clinton, 1992; Nebraska Senator Robert Kerrey, 1992
- Political Activity and Department (Box 13, Folder 7)
  Includes - Former California Governor Edmund G. "Jerry" Brown, 1992; Former MA. Senator Paul Tsongas, 1992; Iowa Senator Tom Harkin, 1992; Ed Koch with Dinkins; ILGWU registering new voters; Governor Jim Florio, David Dinkens; Senator John Heinz at ILG headquarters, Philadelphia, PA, 1988; Mario Cuomo, 1986; House Speaker Thomas P. O'Neill Jr. with AFL-CIO pres. Lane Kirkland and Sec'y-Treas. Thomas R. Donohue, 1986; Congressman Barney Frank, 1986; New England VP Ron Alman, 1986; US Senate candidate Harriet Woods, 1986; Herman Badillo for Congress, 1986; David Dinkens, 1986; Pres. Jay Mazur at City Hall, 1986; Mazur endorses Dinkins at City Hall, 1993; Voting Booth, 1992
- Puerto Rico (Box 14, Folder 1)
  Includes Workers at Barranquitas, 1995; Vice Pres. Torres, 1995; Puerto Rico coastline, 1993; Workers at Bali Bra, 1987; Workers at Ariela, 1990; Dionisio Pellot, president of the Stride Rite organizing committee, 1990; VP Torres and Organizing Dir. Radames Acosta, 1991; Pres. Jay Mazur swearing in VP Torres, 1989; Workers from Panty, Matic, San Juan, 1987; Rally at Bali Bra, 1987; Strikers at Treasure Master's headquarters, Derry, NH, 1988; Bali workers with VP Cliff Depin, 1987; Bali ILGers receive backpay checks, 1988; VP Cliff Depin and Asst. Regional Dir. Jose Torres, 1988; Computer time clock, 1987; VP Torres, 1987; Gen. Sec'y-Treas. Jay Mazur with newly elected officials, 1986; VP Depin with Irwin Solomon & wife, 1987; Gen Sec'y Treas. Solomon at ribbon cutting ceremony, 1987; VP Depin at pact meeting, 1988
- Quilts (Box 14, Folder 2)
  Includes Quilts done by ILGers for a Justice article
- Retirees (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Includes Members of the Newburgh Retiree Club, NY, (circa 1980's); Westchester Retirees Club, Rockland, NY; Florida retirees; Cleveland, OH retirees; Members of Local 324 Retiree Club, RI; NYC retirees club; Members of the South FL retirees club, 1990; Retirees learn bead work, 1990; Club Pres. Stella England at GEB, with Judith Wineman, 1990; VP Evelyn Dubrow, 1990; Members of Rockland County, NY retirees club, 1990; ILG retirees at Midwest/Central conference, 1990; Evelyn Moniz with Millie Burrows of Bristol Elder Services, 1990; Pacific Northwest Dis. Mgr. Katie Quan, San Francisco, CA, 1990; Jerry Gingrich, mgr. of the Northern Dis. Council, 1990; Mohawk Valley Club Members, 1990; NJ retirees conference, 1990; Florida Assoc. of Retirees Club with banner, 1990; Pres. Jay Mazur and Retiree Svc. Dir. Judith Wineman, 1990; Members of the Decatur, Ill retiree club, 1991; Retirees say "Union Yes" to PA senator Harris Wooford, 1991; Retiree VP Lou Montenegro with members, Clinton, IO, 1991
- Retirees (Box 14, Folder 4)
  Includes Retirees from Easton, PA, 1991; Dir. Wineman with Bay Area retirees, 1991; New Central PA retirees, 1991; Union's "Friendly Visitor Program", 1991; Retirees, Lancaster, PA, 1991; Millie DiGiorgio celebrates 100th birthday, 1991; "Retiring Right" program, NJ & NY, 1991; Florida retirees, 1991; Upper South retirees, 1990; Members of the New England Assoc. of Retirees Club, 1991; Retired ILGers from Gossard apparel factory, 1991; Pauline Pepe, one of the last remaining survivor of the Triangle Shirtwaist Fire at 100 years of age, (circa 1990's)
- Retirees (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Includes Puerto Rico retirees club, 1991; AIM director Martin Berger with first retiree AIM chapter, 1991; Delina Chouvette turns 100, 1991; Nassau County's retirees club, NY, 1991; "Express Yourself Players", 1991; Florida retirees, 1991; Local 109 retirees with Senator Harris Wooford, Scranton, PA; 1993; ILGWU retirees support the work of "On the Mend", 1993; Pres. Jay Mazur and NYC Mayor David Dinkins1993; Members of the Hazelton, PA retirees club, 1994; Vice Pres. Susan Cowell, 1994; Union Health Center, 1994; Union Health Center educator Kathleen Schwartz, 1994; Members of Brooklyn retirees club, 1994; Retirees luncheon, Newburgh, PA, 1995; Vice Pres. Sal Giardina with retirees, 1995; South Jersey Retiree Club at Unity House, 1986; Local 120 retirees club, Decatur, III, 1986; Retirees participate in FLEX Exercise Program, 1986; Members of Montreal retiree club, 1986; Members of New Haven, CT retiree club, 1986; Baltimore retirees, 1987; Chicago retirees, 1987; Retirees, Elizabeth, NJ, 1987; Baltimore retirees, 1987; ILGWU organizer Gasper Sciacca and Nassau-Suffolk District council mgr., 1987
- Retirees (Box 14, Folder 6)
  Includes VP Clifford Depin with Puerto Rican retirees, 1987; ILG veteran Abraham Marchuck celebrates 100th birthday, 1987; Dir. Judith Wineman with Florida retirees, 1987; Association of Retiree Clubs (ARC) VP Mac Abrams and Pres. Al Glenn, 1987; ARC luncheon, Pompano Beach, FL, 1987; New Port Richey retiree club, FL, 1987; ILGWU Asst. Pres. Gus Tyler, FL, 1987; Exec. VP Wilbur Daniels with retirees, NY, 1987; Easton Club retirees, PA, 1987; Mohawk Valley, NY retirees, 1987; Retirees at the Caton Manor Nursing Home, Baltimore, MD, 1987; St. Petersburg retirees club members, 1987; Local 295 retirees, Pittston, PA, 1987; Long Branch NJ retirees club, 1987; Paterson NJ Friendly Senior Club, 1987; Members of the Cleveland, OH retirees club, 1987; Members of the Shamokin-Sunbury Pottsville District Council, 1987; The Cumberland Valley Retirees Club, Central PA, 1987; Mohawk Valley retirees club, 1987; Gainesville, PA retirees club, 1987; Retirees of Hialeah, FL on trip to Santo Domingo, 1987; Workers of Retiree Service Dept., 1987; Members of the Southern New England District Council, 1988; NY retirees hold meetings, 1986; Retirees of Gerald Mills, Inc., Hazelton, PA, 1986; Kingston NY president with Stanley Lundine, Democratic candidate for lieutenant governor, 1986; New Bedford, MA retirees, 1986; Rhode Island retirees, 1986; Nassau County retirees, 1986; Baltimore retirees club meeting, 1986; Suffolk County retirees picnic, 1986; Westchester retirees club, 1986; ILG Nassau County Retiree Club with Pres. Jay Mazur, VP Sal Giardina, director of NY State District, VP Evelyn Dubrow, 1986; State Attorney General Robert Abrams addresses retirees, 1986; Rhode Island retirees, 1988; Baltimore retirees, 1988; Upstate NY retirees, 1988
- Retirees (Box 14, Folder 7)
  Includes NJ retirees club, 1988; Local 99 retirees club, 1988; Local 102 retirees club, 1988; Local 122 retirees club, Atlanta GA, 1988; Mike Trinchi, Lower Hudson District Council mgr., 1988; Cumberland Valley Retiree Club, PA, 1988; Retirees exercise club, 1988; ILGWU Retiree Service Dept. Director Matthew Schoenwald with Dr. Eugene Callender, director of the NY State Office of the Aging, 1988; Pre-retirement planning seminar, Puerto Rico, 1988; Pres. Jay Mazur, 1988; ILGWU celebrate the holidays, Chinatown NY, 1987; Retiree Service Director Matthew Schoenwald with retirees, 1988; Florida retirees, 1987; Members of the South River Retirees Club, NJ, 1986; Some ILG retirees married 50 years, Long Island, NY, 1989; Silver Needle Award winners, 1989; NYC retirees for David Dinkins, 1989; NYC Mayor Dinkins, 1989
- Retirees 92 - 93 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Includes Chicago retirees at rally outside of Prudential Insurance Co. headquarters, 1994; Members of Florida Retiree Club 7, 1994; Nassau County Retiree Club, 1995; Florida Association of Retirees, 1995; Wilkes-Barre, PA retirees club, 1995; Ethel Messinger receives Friendly Visitor award, 1994; Friendly Visitor Workshop, 1994; Rose Itrs, 1995; Health Care rally, 1994; NJ Retiree Council meeting, 1994; Dorothy and Edwin Francis, 1995; Mae McHugh with senator Ralph Musto, 1995; Deerfield, FL retiree club, 1995; Nassau County Retiree Club, 1995; ILGers at National Council of Senior Citizens, 1994; Sweetwater Club #2, 1994; Milwaukee club meeting, 1994; Express Yourself players, 1994; Gov. Mario Cuomo, 1994; On the Mend Program, 1994; Phil Donahue with Anita Raposa, 1993; NYC Mayor Dinkins, 1993; Hialeah retiree club #9, 1993; Retirees at Clinton/Gore Rally, 1992
- Retirees 92 - 93 (Box 15, Folder 1a)